doc I got this rash that won't go away
I've tried everything radiation dirt
radioactive dirt have you tried
bandaging your mouth would that help
would help me my queen your voice ever
sonorous is like a gentle waterfall upon
my ears right after the mission mark my
words yeah the ears are
next it's so hard to tell right wrong if
only I had someone to give me guidance
mhm someone wise and experienced an
adoptive mother if you will oh no
absolutely
not if you know what you're looking for
inquiry is unnecessary but if you don't
know how do you inquire ah Zeno's
Paradox look at us too Superstars out
and about uh what we should keep our
heads down we don't want the paparazzi
finding us right it's probably risky for
us to talk at
all Peter Piper pick the p no Peter
Piper pick up are you people always this
loud don't lump Us in with him he's not
with us he's not with us he's uh not
with
us I was just in the kitchen
anyone have something they want to
confess I was just trying to make a
milkshake how come you don't stay a big
BL all the time I prefer tactical
Precision over Brute Force oh likewise
likewise some of my favorite boms are
extraordinarily
precise so how'd you P this heists boms
uh-huh and was was there Sur there to be
another step get this more
boms what's wrong man it's nothing just
beginning to think nobody likes me maybe
if you stop stealing and blowing up
everybody's stuff is it even worth it if
I don't get to do what I
love how many of you OverWatch people
are missing an eye I don't need two eyes
to swing a hammer how many of you
Scoundrels are missing a
leg sticky bombs what a fantastic idea
how do they work that is classified
information no worries I'll figure it
out on me own all I need is some
glue when I look at you I see pure
unadulterated chaos is it the bombs you
don't like the
bombs jamus and fox interviewing this
fancy robot any wisdom to share with us
as the battle begins Victory goes to
those who maintain their focus boring
back to you Natasha any car Chas this is
we could watch so I'm trying to ask
everybody this what is your favorite
animal I've always wanted a guinea pig
I'd name it Melrose uh yeah I can see it
I like what you got going on the ghost
Powers the magically replenishing
shotguns the mysterious identity you're
a real character shut
up so did you have a chance to think
about my proposal I'm not putting
explosives on my maze what oh no no no
no no you misunderstood I was talking
about your Shield that's even
worse one stick of dynamite well that's
just adorable Bob I meant admirable
admirable look it's the strangest spot
I've ever seen that's all I'm saying
strangeness is in the eye of the
beholder oh no he heard me this is so
awkward
those who seek only to enrich themselves
live the most impoverished lives of
all that's why I'm an
artist are you and Road Hog together do
you ever see us apart no I mean are you
a couple yes a couple of Dashing rugs
not sure what you're missing here
doomfist Doom
fist it's a great name what's yours they
call me jrat not as good no not as good
Jameson Fox reporting live let's ask
this scary metal black how he thinks the
battle's going to go you are not a
journalist a puzzling prognostication
now back to Natasha for a look at the
weather we should do a concert together
oh what do you play uh I sing
I
sing I
sing I sing fig fig fig fig fig
fig wow yeah uh I'll have to get back to
you on that what's on your mind mate I
am thinking of what I have lost what
your keys arrows snacks I've got snacks
cheer up didn't I say I'd rip out your
tongue if I saw you
again Jameson VX Channel 9 News Mr
GunBot sir how do you think the battle's
going to
[Applause]
go could you repeat that in words hold
on breaking news the moon has fallen
into the
ocean anyone want to hear my favorite
joke about the periodic product table I
don't know will it make me go he he
h we're more medled than mate you and I
why we could be
twins and I was having such a nice
day roadhog take them head on got it hey
I want a mission too try not to blow
yourself up a but it's me
specialty you looking for a lab assist
I'm gr with chemicals certainly we would
begin by testing your tolerance for pain
uh what's pain have to do with science
everything My Strange little
friend Jameson FKS and to bjorland home
two handsome Geniuses just chitchatting
away you can't be serious don't be so
hard on
yourself I've met mozes with more brains
than you FKS with all the respect m I
believe that's a knock against the
junker Town education system we've got
an education
system it's a perfect day for some
Mayhem that's what I'm always saying
wouldn't a scythe be more on brand I
prefer shotguns can't really Harvest
with them but who am I to argue with
death
himself me might R hog says it's a
fetching price on your nuggin not as
high as the one on ours mind you he said
all that he was more like going to turn
that BL in with a heap thank you for the
warning and the convincing
impression cheers love it's time to save
the world oh what
again you got a problem
junker I don't do problems just
Solutions
yeah United again the OverWatch Strike
Team prepares for Action hey keep the
Cals clear please this is the discipline
the commander is known for I'm about to
be known for kicking your butt uh champ
which of your glorious victories was
your favorite hamster is tired of your
questions mine was when you beat three
I'm Luke oh you gave him the what
forall hey rocket lady did they make
that suit in my
size oh oh you couldn't handle one of
these why not I was born to
fly I was thinking of becoming an
underwear model how does one get pecks
as hulking as yours you wouldn't like it
why does it include work I can't stand
work I wanted to go to the beach earlier
but some miniac stole all the volleyball
nits why would someone do that unless
they had a brilliant
plan my exquisitus queen I come bearing
news of great import not now rat junk my
name's junkrat now it isn't trust me
everyone with Bastion on our side this
is going to go
great who the bot I thought he was
decorative well I'm happy to have you
you rob any train in your day they get
all gummed up together in a big pile
when I try you're supposed to stop them
first I do stop them I think my problem
is that I stopped them a little too
hard I feel sorry for your doctor she's
the best in the outback Jord you mean
pyro Mania I think you mean pyrro Mania
that one I'm still seeing a for you look
like a gentleman who eat his own tin
Nails why the hell would you say that to
someone just looking for something we
might have in common